[{"question":"In Agile development, When does Acceptance Testing is performed?","answers":["Before the product is shipped to the customer","On request of the customer","At the end of every day","At the end of each iteration"],"correct_ans":4,"level":1,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"What User Stories describe?","answers":["Feedback from users about the end-product","A software feature from an end-user perspective","Feedback from customers about the end-product","The users experience of the last iteration"],"correct_ans":2,"level":2,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"What is the IEEE 830?","answers":["A verification and validation document (V\u0026V)","A software requirements specification (SRS) ","A software quality assurance document (SQA)","A software test documentation"],"correct_ans":2,"level":3,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"Software Requirement Specification (SRS) is also known as specification of .....?","answers":["White box testing ","Acceptance testing","Integrated testing","Black box testing "],"correct_ans":4,"level":3,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"What is done during a Sprint Review Meeting?","answers":["Testing of classes and methods","Demo of the current Iteration","Financial planning of the project","Aceeptance Testing"],"correct_ans":2,"level":1,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"When does a Sprint Review Meeting occurs?","answers":["At the end of the current iteration","At the final stage of the project","Whenever the developers want","At the start of each day"],"correct_ans":1,"level":1,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"Which of the following is a Creational Design Pattern?","answers":["Command Pattern","Singleton Pattern","Observer Pattern","Iterator Pattern"],"correct_ans":2,"level":2,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"Which of the following is a Behavioral Design Pattern?","answers":["Observer Pattern","Facade Pattern","Builder Pattern","Adapter Pattern"],"correct_ans":1,"level":2,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"Which of the following is the most important area of concern in cloud computing?","answers":["Security","Speed","Scalability","Storage"],"correct_ans":1,"level":1,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"Which of the following architectural standards is working with cloud computing?\n","answers":["Standardized Web services","Web-application frameworks","Service-oriented architecture","All of the Mentioned"],"correct_ans":3,"level":2,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"What is the meaning of Corrective Software Maintenance?","answers":["Adapt the system to a different environment","Fixing a bug detected by the Scrum Master","Modifying the system to satisfy new requirements","Fixing unpredicted bugs/issues after shippment"],"correct_ans":4,"level":3,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"What is the meaning of Adaptive Software Maintenance?","answers":["Modifying the system to satisfy new requirements","Correcting bugs detected by the QA team","Adapt the system to new security requirements","Adapt the system to a different environment"],"correct_ans":4,"level":1,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"According to Quality Management Standards, What is a Quality Assurance Audit?","answers":["Systematic inspection of code documentation","Systematic inspection of the company\u0027s processes","Examination of feedback from customers","Examination of feedback from developers"],"correct_ans":2,"level":3,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"Which of the following is NOT a level of CMM (Capability Maturity Modwdwdel)?","answers":["Optimizing","Repeatable","Defined","Documenting"],"correct_ans":4,"level":3,"team":"Viper"},{"question":"Which of the following is a creational design pattesdsdsrn?","answers":["Singleton","Adapter","Shape Factory","Decorator"],"correct_ans":1,"level":1,"team":"Viper"}]